freeprestashopmodules.com 2012-08-31

# 1&1 Internet - Privacy Policy

1&1 Internet Ltd. is committed to respecting privacy of customers and users of the 1&1 website. 

This privacy policy governs the manner in which 1&1 Internet, Ltd. (1&1) uses, maintains and discloses information collected from customers and users of the 1&1 Website. 

## Privacy

1&1 is committed to developing long lasting relationships based on trust. 1&1 will do everything in its power to ensure that your right to privacy is maintained and protected. This Website is not directed at children under 13 years of age. 

## Information 1&1 Collect

1&1 may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information. The information 1&1 collects is personal information that identifies you personally, such as: 

  * Your name
  * E-mail address
  * Postal address
  * Telephone and facsimile numbers
  * URL
  * Credit card information
  * Other billing information

1&1 may also collect information on how users access the Website by using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies. 

## What are Cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. 1&1 may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by 1&1 to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimise load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by 1&1 to store, for example, whetheror not you want your password remembered, or other such information. Cookies used on the 1&1 Website do not contain personally identifiable information. 

## Log Files

Like most standard Websites, 1&1 use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in the 1&1 log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information. 

## How 1&1 uses this information

1&1 may use the personally identifiable information collected by 1&1 to contact customers regarding products and services offered by 1&1 and, to the extent the User has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 1&1 may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of Website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. 1&1 will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it, unless you specifically authorise such disclosures. 

## Disclosure of Information

1&1 may also disclose aggregate, anonymous, data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, statistical information only will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case 1&1 is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners. 

1&1 may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyse or otherwise store or manipulate data received by 1&1 from its customers. In all such cases, such third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as 1&1 and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy. 

For all domain registrations your registrant details are passed to the domain registrar in accordance with the [Domain Terms and Conditions](http://registrarterms.1and1.co.uk/). Only .UK domains offer an Opt-Out for personal registrations. 

## Special Offers and Updates

1&1 customers and users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and possibly a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of users, 1&1 presents the option to not receive these types of communications. 

## Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, a service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

## Legal Disclaimer

Though every effort is made to preserve your privacy, 1&1 may need to disclose personal information when required to by law. If it is deemed necessary that such action needs to be taken, 1&1 will comply with judicial proceedings should a court order or legal process be served on 1&1\. 

The 1&1 Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that 1&1 is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. You are encouraged to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. The 1&1 Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by 1&1\. 

## Maintenance of Information

The information provided to 1&1 is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by 1&1\. 1&1 employs industry standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. Although 1&1 cannot guarantee that any loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; every effort is made to prevent such occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as payment details collected for commercial transactions, is encrypted prior to transmission by you to 1&1\. 

## Your Responsibility

You are responsible for the security of your Account Number and passwords. Make sure you keep it in a safe place and do not share it with others.  
Always remember to log out after your session ends, to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home. 

## Questions

Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy may be directed by e-mail to [PrivacyPolicy@1and1.co.uk](mailto:PrivacyPolicy@1and1.co.uk).
